Welcome back to my channel in
this video I will discuss Mas again
about insurance and finance, yes,
but before I continue for
friends who have just visited
and joined our channel, we
support you by sharing
this video so that this channel's status
develops and can provide
useful information
about financial achievements and trading in
our next videos
Okay, let's try to continue the discussion in
this video about one of the
leading insurance in Indonesia, namely FWD,
yes,
so there are various products that, for example, can be
tailored to your needs,
such as life insurance, health selection,
accident insurance, or investment, yes,
for those of you who want to invest,
please just click here.
What is the difference between FWD
and other insurance, which is definitely a
negative product, so this
offers a product that is easy to understand
and also for the claim process, it is also
very easy, very convenient,
so insurance is also a digital type of insurance
and
access to the right assistance
and using FPD Max insurance,
yes, So, how many features are the advantages of
FPB insurance and this is access to
polyp information for our learning
and monitoring investment results and also
you can change our data,
update your personal data, you can
submit claims and check your status
and there are how many insurances or
protections from life insurance, yes, there
are PD critical plus  protection there is
insurance data plan and beta insurance
free plan only this and there are many
more types of insurance variants both our
life and health insurance
so for insurance
provides easy protection if
for this free plan sanction
this family will always be the
main priority so this is
optimal free plan insurance protection
there is also health insurance yes comes
with flexible benefits yes without having to
pay very high premiums
and there are many types of protection protection
from this FB insurance which is
different from other insurance
because many products are offered there are
also investment units yes So this is a
kind of insurance which is a
real number so this issues
lifetime protection while we invest
[Music]
I also use the fpd elite link yes
so insurance provides the opportunity
to develop your assets so that
your dreams in the future can be
achieved
Okay
one of Indonesia's leading insurance
is the fwd transaction yes if
you like this video don't
forget to always support our channel
And delivered useful information
wassalamualaikum warahmatullahi
wabarakatuh